Guide to the Elayne Zalis video studies archive, [circa 1979-1997].
Zalis, Elayne video studies archive
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Elayne Zalis video studies archive, [circa 1979-1997].
8231
Zalis, Elayne.
8 cubic feet.
Printed material, Publications, Videotapes
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Research and study materials related to Zalis’ academic work on the history and practice of video art at the University of Iowa and the Long Beach Museum. Includes many significant video artworks on video cassette, related bibliographies, and lists of significant video art production, study and distribution sources during 1980s and 1990s.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Elayne Zalis received her B.A. in 1975 from the University of Florida in Gainesville and studied library science at Simmons College in Boston, Massachusetts, in 1976. After receiving her M.A. in journalism and scriptwriting at the University of Florida in 1983, Zalis enrolled at the University of Iowa, where she worked with the Special Collections Department of the University of Iowa Libraries on its Artists Television Project. In 1993, she completed her Ph.D. at the University of Iowa in Interdisciplinary Studies, with a focus on humanities and the media arts.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection includes study tapes, catalogues, and correspondence that document the history of U.S. video art. This range of materials documents developments in independent American video throughout the 25-year period of its most significant production, from 1977-1992. These materials provided the background for Elayne Zalis's Ph.D. dissertation on humanities and the media arts at the University of Iowa. The collection also includes the manuscripts and printed editions of Zalis's own multimedia quartet, Recycled Memories. In addition to 150 video tapes available for reference, the Zalis Archive includes a wide range of original exhibition catalogues and monographs on national and international video art, as well as research materials on independent distributors, festivals, and media centers in the 1980s. This collection documents the work of individual artists, group exhibitions, video festivals, distributors, and agencies and sources of commissioned video art, while providing a snapshot of the history of America video art: its production, exhibition, and critical evaluation.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Zalis, Elayne.; Zalis, Elayne.; Rose Goldsen Archive of New Media Art.
Subjects:
Video art.
Form and Genre Terms:
Videotapes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Elayne Zalis Creative Works
Boxes 1, 2
Series II. Published Material
Boxes 1, 2
Series III. Alphabetic Subject Files
Boxes 3-6
Series IV. Videos
Boxes 7-10
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Elayne Zalis Creative Works
  - Recycled Memories: A Multimedia Quartet Elayne Zalis, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    DVD
  - Vagabond Scribe (Leah’s Backstory), 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    book/novel
  - Arella’s Repertoire Elayne Zalis, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Virtual Dayz: Remediated Visions and Digital Memories Elayne Zalis, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    book/blog
  - Micellaneous papers Elayne Zalis (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Papers, photocopies, syllabi. Not Zalis’ original file; miscellaneous papers included with shipment of her creative works. Includes photocopy of photobooth portraits of the artist.
- Series II. Published Material
  - The First Generation, Women and Video 1970-75 Hanley, JoAnn, ed., 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    NY: Independent Curators Inc.
    monograph/catalogue
  - The Second Link: Viewpoints on Video in the Eighties, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Banff: Walter Phillips Gallery
  - Video: A Retrospective Long Beach Museum of Art 1974-1984 Huffman, Kathy Rae, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Long Beach: Long Beach Museum of Art
  - TV Generations Baldessari, John and Yonemoto, Bruce, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    LA: Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions (LACE)
  - Surveillance Miller, Branda and Irmas, Deborah, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Video: A Retrospective Long Beach Museum of Art 1974-1984 Huffman, Kathy Rae, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Premier Issue, Winter
    journal
  - At Home Raven, Arlene, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The Dawn of Sound Bandy, Mary Lea, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    NY: Museum of Modern Art
  - Art + Telecommunication Grundmann, Heidi, ed., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Wien/Vancouver: Western Front
    monograph/catalogue (in German)
  - Alternatives in Retrospect: an Historical Overview, 1969-1975 Apple, Jacki, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    NY: The New Museum
  - Picture This: Films Chosen by Artists Gallagher, Steve, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Buffalo: Hallwalls
  - Video By Artists 2 Town, Elke, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Toronto: Art Metropole
  - New Tapes, New Artists, New Video from Europe, 1985 Electronic Arts Intermix, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    rental/collection catalogue
  - Third World Newsreel, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    20th Anniversary Issue
  - Third World Newsreel, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    25th Anniversary Issue
  - Women Make Movies, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Video Tape Catalogue 1, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Syracuse University: Synapse Video Center
  - Video Tape Review 86 Video Data Bank, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    rental/collection catalogue (2 copies)
  - Early Video Art in the United States Video Data Bank (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Women Make Movies, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Video Electronic Arts Intermix, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Media '92, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    pamphlet/poster/event publicity information
  - “Censoring the Media” Issue of Felix, vol. 1, no. 1 (Spring 1991), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - “Shot/Reverse Shot: A Cross-Circuit Videologue” Issue of Felix, vol. 1, no. 2 (Spring 1992), 1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - “Postliterate” Issue of Felix, vol. 1, no. 3, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - “Sex, Performance, and the 80s” Double issue of The Flue, Franklin Furnace Archive., vol. 2. no. 3, 1983., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - New Listings Video Data Bank, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    December 1992
  - Revising Romance: New Feminist Video Podheiser, Linda and Riley, Bob (Box 1, Folder 33)
    American Federation of Arts/ ICA Boston
    pamphlet/poster/publicity information
  - Console-ing Passions: Television, Video, and Feminism Video Data Bank, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Tucson 1994
    conference program
  - AFI Los Angeles International Film Festival 1997, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    publicity packet / press release
  - Women in the Director’s Chair Film and Video Festival, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    March 1992
    pamphlet/poster/event information
  - Video Center for New Television, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Nov-Dec 1991
    newsletter
  - Scanlines, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Vol. 1 no. 5, Nov-Dec 1991
  - UCLA film and television archive, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - New Artists, New Tapes, special series Electronic Arts Intermix (Box 1, Folder 40)
    rental/collection catalogue, with Zalis’ notes (2 copies)
  - Hallwalls, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Jan-Feb 1992
  - Tonantzin, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Intelligente Ambiente, special series, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Ars Electronica 1994
  - Movement Research, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Vol. 3, Fall 1991
  - Alive TV, summer session, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - New Day Films.Film and Video Catalgoue, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Intermedia Arts Minnesota, Video catalog, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Into Video Art: The Characteristics of a Medium Perrée, Bob. Trans. A.H.W. Karelse, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Rotterdam and Amsterdam: Rumore, 1988
    monograph/catalogue; photocopy; in English and Dutch
  - Video Catalogus Kijkhuis (Box 1, Folder 49)
    rental/collection catalogue; 3-ring binder, in English and Dutch
  - Independent Video, Alternative Media Video Data Bank (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - On Art and Artists Video Data Bank, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Video Tape Review Video Data Bank, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Video Tape Review, 1987-1991 Video Data Bank, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    rental/collection catalogue (with Zalis’ notes)
  - File: Video Bibliography by Genre (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Printed and photocopied handwritten pages, in mailing envelope from Vision 26, 1992
    bibliography
  - File: Video Conference: Conosole-ing Passions 4/92, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Programs etc from conference, Iowa City, 1992
  - File: Dissertation—Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 7)
    letters to and from Zalis from artists, institutions, etc.
  - File: Video art (newspaper articles) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    photocopies of newspaper articles about video art
  - The American Film Institute Advanced Technology Programs The American Film Institute, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Winter 1993
  - File: ABCNEWS Moving Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Thick packet of photocopies from newspapers, journals, and other sources
    (Note: not Zalis’ original file or title)
  - File: Video Art—Bibliography 1989, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    bibliography, assembled by Zalis
  - File: Thesis (Master’s) Kathy Huffman Huffman, Kathy (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - File: Video Includes: Afterimage Sept. 1987, Goldman, Debra,, “AIVF at 10: A History;” The Independent Jan./Feb. 1985, Thomon, Patricia, “Surviving the Eighties: Global Village’s 14th Annual Documentary Festival;” The Independent Oct. 1988; etc., 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Tape: An international conference on the issues of technology, aesthetics, politics, education, and entertainment in the multimedia environment, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Alive TV, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Independent Images Tour Southwest Alternate Media project, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    pamphlet/poster/event information, mailing envelope
  - Inter.com Interactive Communications Society, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Jan. 1995
  - Saint-gervais geneve Semaine internationale de video, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Playback 1996 video preservation roundtable, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Three Sites/ Multiple Views CalArts, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    April 1996
  - Exhibitions list (Box 2, Folder 21)
    computer printout with Zalis’ notes
  - Visible Evidence II: Strategies and practices in documentary film and video University of Southern California (USC), 1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    August 1994
  - ISEA 1995, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    event outline
  - Private TV Public Living Rooms LA Freewaves, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    pamphlet/poster/event information, packet
  - Intermedia Arts Minnesota, Artist services information (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 4th Celebration of Independent Video LA Freewaves, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - File: Feminist Video—what does she want? (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Photocopied articles on feminist video
  - MAIN Media Arts Information Network, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    September 1991
  - File: Video Art – Articles (general) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    Photocopies and clippings of articles on video art
  - 20th anniversary raffle posters Anthology Film Archives (Box 2, Folder 30)
    pamphlet/poster/event information, mailing envelope, includes letter from Jonas Mekas, artistic director
  - The Learning Channel, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - National Video Festival American Film Institute, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - AIVF Guide to International Film and Video Festivals Bowser, Kathryn, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    NY: Foundation for Independent Video and Film, 1988
  - AFI Los Angeles International Film Festival, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - AFI National Video Festival, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Course reader packet: Elayne Zalis Video Self-Portraits, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Spring 1991
    Spiral bound photocopies of essays and articles.
  - Video Preservation: Securing the Future of the Past Boyle, Deirdre, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    NY: Media Alliance, 1993
    white paper
  - San Francisco Video Festival, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - The Bottom Line: Funding for Media Arts Organizations Adams, Don; Goldbard, Arlene, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    National Alliance for Media Arts and Culture (NAMAC)
  - IICS (International Interactive communications Society) Membership Directory, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Notes: Video / list or outline (Box 2, Folder 41)
    Single page, written by Zalis
  - AFI National Film Festival thirteenth national video festival American Film Institute, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - AFI Los Angeles International Film Festival American Film Institute, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Young, British and Black: a monograph on the work of the Sankofa film/video collective and Black audio film collective Fusco, Coco, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    Buffalo: Hallwalls, 1988
  - Cinema Mexico tribute to contemporary Mexican cinema (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - World Wide Video Festival, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    The Hague, 1988
    monograph/catalogue, in Dutch and English
  - American Film Institute, National Video Festival American Film Institute, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Intermental 9: Herz von Europe/Heart of Europe, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    Wein, 1989
    monograph/catalogue, in German and English
  - American Film Institute, National Video Festival American Film Institute, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - American Film Institute, National Video Festival American Film Institute, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - American Film Institute, National Video Festival American Film Institute, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - AFI National Video Festival American Film Institute, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - AFI National Video Festival American Film Institute, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - New California Video: A Survey of Open Channels Nash, Michael, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    Long Beach: Long Beach Museum of Art, 1990
  - Family Stories Georgia, Olivia, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    State Island: Newhouse Center for Contemporary Art, 1990
  - Difference: on representation and sexuality Linker, Kate, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    NY: New Museum of contemporary art, 1984
    monograph/catalogue, includes essays by Ownes, Linker; Tickner, Rose; Wollen, Weinstock
  - Utopia Post Utopia: Configurations of Nature and Culture in Recent Sculpture and Photography The Institute of Contemporary Art (ICA), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    Cambridge, MIT Press, 1988
    monograph/catalogue, includes essays by Jameson, Jardine; Joselit, Michaud; Solomon-Godeau, Sussman
  - Installation: Video Denson, Roger G., and High, Kathy, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    Buffalo: Hallwalls Contemporary Art Center, 1981
  - Building Paranoia: The Proliferation of Interdictory Space and the Erosion of Spatial Justice Flusty, Steven, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    LA: Los Angeles Forum for Architecture and Urban Design, 1994
  - Prime Time Video Hanhardt, John G., et al, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Saskatoon: Mendel Art Gallery, 1984
  - Infermental: A Travelling Exhibition of World Video Hill, Chris; Conrad, Tony; Weibel, Peter, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Buffalo, New York Edition, Hallwalls, 1988
  - Virtual Seminar on the Bioapparatus Richards, Catherine; Tenhaaf, Nell, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Banff: Banff Center, 1991
    monograph/catalogue, includes letter to Zalis from Fred Truck, 8/20/1992
  - The Art of Memory/ The Loss of History Olander, William, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Video Witnesses: Festival of New Journalism Hill, Chris, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Buffalo: Hallwalls Contemporary Art Center, 1991
  - American Landscape Video: the electronic groove Judson, William, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Pittsburgh: Carnegie Museum of Art, 1988
  - About Time: Video, Performance, and Installation by 21 Women Artists Institute of Contemporary Arts, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    London: ICA, 1980
  - FAKE Olander, William, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    NY: The New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1987
  - Voyager software catalog, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Tenth Anniversary, 1977-87 New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Eleventh Anniversary New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Twelfth Anniversary New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Films of Andy Warhol Whitney Museum of Art, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Sound and Vision: Musikvideo und Filmkunst Deutsches filmmuseum, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Hamburg, 1994
  - Infermental: The first international magazine on videocassettes, 1980-86, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    journal, in German
  - Native Americans on Film and Video, Volume II Weatherford, Elizabeth; Suebert, Emellia, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    NY: Museum of the American Indian, 1988
  - 3-ring binder of information on video festivals national and international, 1981-1989 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    organized by Zalis 1981-1989
  - 3-ring binder of information on museums and exhibiting venues (Box 3, Folder 18)
    organized by Zalis
  - File: Curated Exhibition—The Body Politic (Bay Area Women, cur. Steve Seid) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - File: Curated Exhibition—The Feminist “I” (Brooklyn Museum, cur. by Women Make Movies) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - File: Curated Exhibition—The Mother and Child Reunion, Long Beach Museum of Art, CA (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - File: Curated Exhibitions—LACE (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - File: Curated Exhibitions—Whitney Lucinda Furlong (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - File: American Film Institute (AFI) Video Festival #1, 1981, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Whitney Museum Publications (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Whitney Museum Publications (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Series III. Alphabetic Subject Files
  - Abbe Don, Videomaker (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Artist Information
  - Acts of Resistance, Video Production Group (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Acts of Resistance Marketing Package, San Francisco, 1990
  - AIDS Video (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Video Against Aids Pamphlet, Video Data Bank, Chicago, 1989
    - Video Against Aids Program Notes, Video Data Bank, Chicago, 1989
  - Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - A Video Vasari Program, Buffalo, NY, 1987
    - A Video Vasari New Titles Index, Buffalo, NY, 1987
  - Alive From Off Center (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Alive From Off Center Background Information, Saint Paul, MN, 1985
    - Alive From Off Center National Showcase Program, 1985 (2)
    - Alive From Off Center National Showcase Program, 1986
    - Alive From Off Center National Showcase Program, 1987
    - Copenhagen Film and Video Workshop Festival Announcement, 1988
    - Shewey, Don, “Alive From Off Center Provides National Exposure for New Generation of Avant-Garde Artists”, New York, 1985
  - American Federation of the Arts (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Revising Romance: New Feminist Video, The American Federation of Arts program, 1984
    - The American Federation of Arts Film/Video Program, 1987
    - The American Federation of Arts Film/Video Program, 1989
    - Whitney Biennial Video Exhibition program, The American Federation of Arts Film program, 1985
    - Whitney Biennial Video Exhibition program, The American Federation of Arts Film program, 1987
  - American Film Institute (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - AFI National Video Festival Pamphlet, 1988
    - AFI National Video Festival Pamphlet, 1989
    - AFI National Video Festival Newspaper Schedule, 1988
    - AFI National Video Festival Distribution List, 1990
    - AFI Television Writers Summer Workshop Announcement Form, 1989
  - American Library Association (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - ALA Annual Conference Schedule, 1990
    - ALA Annual Conference Program, 1990
  - Angles: Women Working in Film (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Angles Quarterly Publication, Vol. 1, No. 1, 1991
    - Angles Quarterly Publication, Vol. 1, No. 2, 1992
    - Angles Quarterly Publication, Vol. 1, No. 3, 1992
    - Angles Quarterly Publication, Vol. 1, No. 4, 1992
    - Angles Quarterly Publication, Vol. 2, No. 1, 1993
  - Ann Arbor 8mm Film Festival (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - 19th Ann Arbor 8mm Film Festival Press Release, 1990
  - Annenberg/CPB Project (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Application Guidelines, 1989
    - Projects Approved to Date, 1989
    - The Annenberg/CPB Collection Video and Audio Catalog, 1989
  - Anstey, Jo (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Jo Anstey, ‘The Bus Stops Here’ Script, 1991
  - Anthology: Doug Hall and Sally Jo Fifer (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Table of Contents for ‘Art Video: An Anthology of Writings on Artists’ Video’
  - Archives of Appalacia (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Archives of Appalacia Newsletter, Vol. III, 1981
    - Archives of Appalacia Brochure
    - The Richard Blausetein Collection Inventory, 1987
  - Archives: MARC Format (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Library of Congress Catalog, ‘Access: Catalogs and Technical Publications for 1989’,1989
    - Library of Congress Catalog, ‘MARC: Distribution Services 1989’, 1989
    - Library of Congress Catalog, ‘Select MARC: Restrospective Conversion Service’, 1989
  - Archives: National Historical Publications and Records Commission (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Annual Report, 1987
    - Records Program Grant Guidelines and Procedures, 1989
  - Archives: Society of American Archivists, Chicago (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - SAA Membership Brochure, 1990
    - SAA Annual Meeting Preliminary Program, 1990
    - SAA Newsletter, May 1990
    - Modern Archives Institute Pamphlet, 1991
  - Archives: UCLA Film and Television Archive (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Screenings and Events Calendar, 1990
  - Art Books: Jaap Rietman, New York (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Art Books Inventory Catalog, No. 30, Fall 1987
    - Art Books Inventory Catalog, No. 31, Spring 1988
  - Art Books: Printed Matter Inc. (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Printed Matter Catalog, Fall 1987
    - Printed Matter Catalog, Christmas 1987
    - Printed Matter Catalog, Fall 1988
    - Invoice Receipt, 1988
    - Printed Matter Flyer, Christmas 1988
    - Printed Matter Flyer, Spring 1989
    - Printed Matter Catalog, Summer 1989
    - Printed Matter Catalog, Christmas 1989
    - Printed Matter Mailing Brochure, 1989
    - Printed Matter Catalog, Spring 1990
    - Printed Matter Flyer, Christmas 1990
  - Art Catalogues, LA (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Exhibition Catalogues on 20th Century Artists, List 13, 1988-1989
    - Exhibition Catalogues on 20th Century Artists, List 14, 1990
  - Art Com, San Francisco (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Selected Bibliography on Video/Television From Art Com Magazine 1975-1985, 1985
    - Art Com Press Release, 1986
    - Tokyo Form and Spirit Flyer, 1987
    - Contemporary Arts Press Distribution, Winter 1987
    - Art Com Press Release, Spring/Summer 1988
    - Contemporary Arts Press Distribution, Summer 1988
    - Contemporary Arts Press Distribution, Winter 1988
    - Art Com Media Distribution Catalog, No. 1, 1988
    - Art Com Video Fall Update, 1989
    - Art Com Press Release, Fall 1989
    - Contemporary Arts Press Distribution Catalog, Fall 1990
    - Art Com Media Distribution Catalog, Winter 1990(2 copies)
    - Art Com Television Distribution: Nam June Paik no date(2 copies)
    - Contemporary Arts Press Distribution: Picture This, no date
  - Art in Form Book and Record Story, Seattle (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Catalog of Books on Contemporary Art, Fall 1988-Winter 1989
    - Art in Form Catalog Five
    - Art in Form Catalog Six
    - Art in Form Catalog Seven
    - Art in Form New Contemporary Art Publications Flyer
    - Art in Form New Music Recordings Flyer
  - Art Institute of Chicago (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Public Program Events Calendar, January-February, 1989
    - Public Program Events Calendar, March-April, 1989
  - Art Strike (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Yawn Sporadic Critique of Culture, No. 1, 1989
    - Yawn Sporadic Critique of Culture, No. 2, 1989
    - Yawn Sporadic Critique of Culture, No. 3, 1989
    - Yawn Sporadic Critique of Culture, No. 4, 1989
    - Yawn Sporadic Critique of Culture, No. 5, 1989
    - Yawn Sporadic Critique of Culture, No. 6, 1989
    - Yawnzzz Sporadic Critique of Culture, Art Strike Cancelled, 1989
  - Asian Cinevision (Box 4, Folder 4)